Wiktor Gołab



600 335 148



wiktor.golab@wp.pl

SOCIAL MEDIA



Wiktor Gołąb



WiktorGolab



wiktorgolab.github.io



PROFILE

I am a third-year student at Adam Mickiewicz University in Poznań, Poland, with a passion for web design, application development and artificial intelligence. My student journey is complemented by practical experience gained through internships and work in the technology industry. During my internship at M3 Group, I worked as a web designer (WordPress) and application designer using FlutterFlow, where I perfected my skills in building user-friendly and responsive web solutions.

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C, Java, Latex, Markdown, Python, WordPress (Elementor, WPBakery), Figma, Gimp, Adobe Premiere Pro, Github, Node.js, MMF2, TGF2, Clickteam Fusion, Flutterflow, SQL, YAML/JSON

EXPERIENCE

05.2024 - 07.2024

M3 Group

Web Administrator, Web Designer, Application Designer, Computer Graphic Designer

- Computer Graphics Design,
- Working on the development of user interfaces for e-commerce platform using WordPress Elementor and WP Bakery technologies and other plugins (i.e. Social media stream, pop-up content, RSS Stream).
- (https://wodnasluzbaratownicza.pl/, https://www.eksero24.pl/)
- Taking care of responsive websites,
- Designing Windows, Linux, Android and iOS applications.

2023 - present

EDU-CZAR

Web Administrator, Web Designer, Computer Graphic Designer

- A complete process of creating and administering a website using WordPress was implemented, adjusting the solutions to meet the educational and communication needs of the organization, friendly to both the child and parent's eye.
- Updating content,
- Introducing new posts.
- (https://educzar.pl/)

2023 - present

DermaEx pert

Web Administrator, Web Designer

- A complete website was created from scratch, using the WordPress platform to provide a
 modern and user-friendly solution. The process included the design of the site's structure
 and layout, as well as the implementation of visual and content elements suited to the
 dermatology industry.
- The focus was on providing a responsive and intuitive user interface.
- (https://dermaexpert.pl/)

EDUCATION

2022 - present

Adam Mickiewicz University in Poznań

IT

LANGUAGES

Polish ★★★★★ English ★★★★

CERTIFICATES

- NVIDIA Fundamentals of Deep Learning (https://learn.nvidia.com/certificates?id=uWONS8_sQN2oUHD2ft7buA),
- NVIDIA Generative AI with Diffusion Models (https://learn.nvidia.com/certificates?id=9Zix086UT-qAQJvnUVagoQ#),
- NVIDIA Fundamentals of Accelerated Computing with CUDA Python (https://learn.nvidia.com/certificates? id=3qqH-ONWR56ThTOpk7KU2Q).

SKILLS

- ✓ Independent work,
- √ Teamwork,
- ✓ Quickness in learning,
- ✓ Creative solutions,
- ✓ Attention to detail,
- ✓ Proficient use of AI models (Chat GPT, diffusion models e.g. St able Diffusion, Topaz Gigapixel AI).

HOBBIES



Music



Games



Movies



Media



Artificial Inteligence

I'm always eager to expand my knowledge and take on new challenges in the world of technology and design:)